Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series VIII. Pamphlets
  - Every Pledge Redeemed (Statement of Governor Dix...), 1911; 6477.PA0192; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Dix, John Alden
  - Taxation Of Foreign Mutual Fire Insurance Companies..., 1908; 6477.PA0193; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Chanler, Lewis S.
  - Which Party Stands On Its Record For Primary Reform?, 1911; 6477.PA0194; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - An Unsere Stammesgenossen!, 1908; 6477.PA0195; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Hauser, Julius
  - A Brief Overview Of Official Record Of James A. Parsons Attorney General, 1914; 6477.PA0196; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Parsons, James A.
  - Manual for election Day November 7 1916...Republican State Committee, 1916; 6477.PA0197; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Lest We Forget!...Issued By The American Party, 1916; 6477.PA0198; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Party: American
  - Speech Of Acceptance Of Samuel Seabury...Candidate For Governor, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0199; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Splendid Efficiency Records of Edward Schoeneck Lieutenant Governor..., ca. 1918; 6477.PA0200; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Schoeneck, Edward
    Election: 1918
  - The Truth About The Mobilization...Of The National Guard, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0201; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Practical Reforms In State's Financial Policy, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0202; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Remarkable Record Of The State Tax Commission, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0203; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Direct Tax In 1915 An Absolute Necessity, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0204; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - For Attorney-General Vote For Egburt E. Woodbury, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0205; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Woodbury, Egburt E.
  - The Democratic Underwood Tariff Law A Colossal Failure and Disastrous..., ca. 1916; 6477.PA0206; Items: 2 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Calder. William M.
  - He Will Represent You: Frederick W. Palmer Candidate For Congress..., ca. 1916; 6477.PA0207; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - William F. McCombs The Man For The United States Senate, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0208; Items: 2 (Box 10)
    Candidate: McCombs, Willaim F.
  - Lest We Forget!...Issued By The American Party, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0209; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Whitman's Wanton Waste, ca. 1916; 6477.PA0210; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Campaign Text-Book A Splendid Record Of The Republican Party..., 1916; 6477.PA0211; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Democratic State Platform 1922, 1922; 6477.PA0212; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Smith, Alfred E.
    Election: 1922
  - Democratic Facts About Republican Figures, ca. 1922; 6477.PA0213; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Voters Bulletin Of Information On Candidates (N.Y. League of Women Voters), 1922; 6477.PA0214; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Facts Versus Flourishes And Ruffles (Compiled...by the Citizens Union), 1921; 6477.PA0215; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Election: 1921
  - Keep the Best Steve Riford Republican-Conservative, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0216; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Riford, Steve
  - Lehrman Governor, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0217; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Lehrman, Lewis
  - Friends Of Matt McHugh Nov. 1 Election Eve Party (Invitation), ca. 1982; 6477.PA0218; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Meaning Of Mario, 1982; 6477.PA0219; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Ray Gallagher Democrat For Comptroller, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0220; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Gallagher, Raymond
  - Moynihan's Laws, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0221; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - You Said You Wanted To Know More...Introducing...Anita Maxwell, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0222; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Maxwell, Anita
  - Cuomo A Governor For All New York, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0223; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - What This District Needs Is An Effective Congressman..., ca. 1982; 6477.PA0224; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Let's Keep Stan Lundine Working for Us, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0225; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Clynes For Council, 1982; 6477.PA0226; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Clynes, Margaret L.
  - Supreme Court Justice...Elect Fauci & Dean, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0227; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Dean, William Tucker
  - Voters In Cortland...And Tompkins Counties Stake A Claim For Your Future, ca. 1982; 6477.PA0228; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - To New York State Cornellians, 1913; 6477.PA0229; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Hiscock, Frank H.
    Election: 1913
  - Why You Should Enroll, 1915; 6477.PA0230; Items: 2 (Box 10)
    Candidate: N/A
  - Visitors Simplified Convention Map Of Chicago, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0231; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Earl Warren For President, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0232; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Warren, Earl
  - Our First President...Our Next President..., ca. 1952; 6477.PA0233; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Candidate: MacArthur, Douglas
    Party: Constitution
  - It's Clear Where Eisenhower Stands, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0234; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - The Case For Ike, ca. 1952; 6477.PA0235; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - New York State Citizens For Eisenhower News Report...Vol 1, No. 2, 1952; 6477.PA0236; Items: 5 (Box 10)
  - This Is The Story Of Texas, 1952; 6477.PA0237; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Songs for Republican Rallies, ca. 1956; 6477.PA0238; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Roll Of Delegates And Alternates To The Republican State Convention, 1954; 6477.PA0239; Items: 1 (Box 10)
    Election: 1954
  - Twenty-Fifth Republican National Convention... Official Convention Program, 1952; 6477.PA0240; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Yearbook New York Republican State Committee, 1952; 6477.PA0241; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - Goldwater Canvasser's Kit, 1964; 6477.PA0242; Items: 12 (Box 17)
  - New Yorkers For Keating Promotional Packet, 1964; 6477.PA0243; Items: 18 (Box 9)
  - Keating Fact Sheets, 1964; 6477.PA0244; Items: 46 (Box 10)
  - Human Events Your Washington Weekly Report, 1964; 6477.PA0245; Items: 3 (Box 17)
  - Re-elect Howard Robison, 1964; 6477.PA0246; Items: 3 (Box 10)
  - Constance E. Cook Will Get Results For You, 1964; 6477.PA0247; Items: 3 (Box 10)
  - Re-elect New York State Senator George R. Metcalf, 1964; 6477.PA0248; Items: 3 (Box 10)
    Candidate: Metcalf, George E.
  - Straight Talk, 1964; 6477.PA0249; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - We Must Now Make A Choice In This Land, 1964; 6477.PA0250; Items: 2 (Box 10)
  - A Team You Can Trust, 1964; 6477.PA0251; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Straightforward That's Goldwater, 1964; 6477.PA0252; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - A Choice Not An Echo!, 1964; 6477.PA0253; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Barry Goldwater Speaks Out On The Issues, 1964; 6477.PA0254; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Tender Letters From Barry Goldwater To His Elder Daughter, 1964; 6477.PA0255; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Barry Goldwater SpeaksOut for A Stronger Republican Party, 1964; 6477.PA0256; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Fast Deal!, 1964; 6477.PA0257; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Barry Goldwater...11 Reasons Why He Wants World Peace!, 1964; 6477.PA0258; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - We Must And We Shall... Acceptance Address By Barry Goldwater, 1964; 6477.PA0259; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Your Job is In The Balance- Which Man Really gives You The Best Deal?, 1964; 6477.PA0260; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Barry Goldwater Of Arizona, 1963; 6477.PA0261; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Let's Put Bob Kennedy To Work For New York, 1964; 6477.PA0262; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Register Register Register And Vote Republican Your 1964 Guide..., 1964; 6477.PA0263; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - N.Y. Is Wide Awaye To the Big Issue..., 1964; 6477.PA0264; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Meet Me At The Nation's Capital On Jan. 3, 1965, 1964; 6477.PA0265; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Keep Keating New York's Own Experienced Corageous Dedicated, 1964; 6477.PA0266; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - For The USA Vote Democratic Nov. 3 ( With Photos of Johnson & Humphrey), 1964; 6477.PA0267; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Meet Bill Miller Republican Candidate For Vice President, 1964; 6477.PA0268; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - From One Older American...To Another, 1964; 6477.PA0269; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Donkey Serenade, 1964; 6477.PA0270; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Facts For Voters 1964 (League Of Women voters Of New York State), 1964; 6477.PA0271; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - 1964 Political Calendar For Tompkins County, 1964; 6477.PA0272; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Tompkins County Republican Party Reference Manual 1964, 1964; 6477.PA0273; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Republican Platform 1964, 1964; 6477.PA0274; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - 4 Steps To Victory "Why Not Victory?" For the Republican Party In '64, 1964; 6477.PA0275; Items: 2 (Box 9)
  - Hubert Horatio Humphrey Candidate..."The Best Man In The United States?", 1964; 6477.PA0276; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Establishment And Vice-Presidents, 1964; 6477.PA0277; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Address Of Sen. Strom Thurmond On The 1964 Presidential Race, 1964; 6477.PA0278; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - ESSO Book Of Presidents And Election Facts, 1964; 6477.PA0279; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Memorandum From Eugene Rossides, Campaign Manager...Senator Keating, 1964; 6477.PA0280; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Kennedy Vs. Keating, 1964; 6477.PA0281; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - New York: the Keating Record, 1964; 6477.PA0282; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Civil Rights And The Real Lyndon Johnson, 1964; 6477.PA0283; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Johnson, Lyndon B.(Anti)
  - The Civil Rights Record Of Lyndon B. Johnson, 1964; 6477.PA0284; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Johnson, Lyndon B. (Anti)
  - Peace, Prosperity, And Corruption (Speech by Thruston B. Morton), 1964; 6477.PA0285; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Administrative Directive To Congress: Let's Not Offend The Soviet Union, 1964; 6477.PA0286; Items: 3 (Box 9)
  - Foreign Relations -- 1964, 1964; 6477.PA0287; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Senate Republican Memo Vol. II, No. 38, 1964; 6477.PA0288; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Why A Democratic Senator Turned Republican, 1964; 6477.PA0289; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Cornell Young Republican October 2 1964, 1964; 6477.PA0290; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - American Politics September 5 1964 Issue No. 2, 1964; 6477.PA0291; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - From Herbert Hoover On His 90th Birthday ( A Reader's Digest Reprint), 1964; 6477.PA0292; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Notice Of Submission Of Proposed Amendments To The State Constitution..., 1964; 6477.PA0293; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Democratic Party Fund Raising Letter from Senator Eugene J. McCarthy, 1964; 6477.PA0294; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - White Paper #3 You're Wrong, Mr. Miller, 1964; 6477.PA0295; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Negro Weekly Supports Goldwater, 1964; 6477.PA0296; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - New York State Students For Lyndon B. Johnson Hubert H. Humphrey..., 1964; 6477.PA0297; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Get On the Johnson, Humphrey, Kennedy Team, 1964; 6477.PA0298; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Why I Am A Republican--Article By Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1964; 6477.PA0299; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Which Trend? Remarks Of Hon. Karl E. Mundt Of South Dakota, 1964; 6477.PA0300; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Unconstitutional Usurpation Of Power--Speech Of Hon. James B. Utt..., 1964; 6477.PA0301; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Congressional Record--House August 20, 1964; 6477.PA0302; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Congressional Record--Senate September 9, 1964; 6477.PA0303; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - End "taberism" Elect Francis J. Souhan Your Congressman, ca. 1960; 6477.PA0304; Items: 4 (Box 11)
  - Look Inside to See What They say About...John Taber, ca. 1960; 6477.PA0305; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Thumbnail Biography Of Richard M. Nixon (Henry Cabot Lodge on Verso), ca. 1960; 6477.PA0306; Items: 4 (Box 11)
  - GOP Achievements 1953-1960 (From Republican National Committee), 1960; 6477.PA0307; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - GOP Achievements 1953-1960 (From New York State Republican...), 1960; 6477.PA0308; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Ten Reasons Why We Should Elect Nixon President, 1960; 6477.PA0309; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Republican Times Are Good Times!, 1960; 6477.PA0310; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Experience Counts Elect Henry Cabot Lodge Vice-President, 1960; 6477.PA0311; Items: 5 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Lodge, Henry Cabot
  - Register Register Register And Vote Republican, 1960; 6477.PA0312; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - New York Pioneers Again 2 Years Of Republican Leadership, 1960; 6477.PA0313; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Nixon And Lodge The Team for America's Future..., 1960; 6477.PA0314; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - For The Future This Is A Time To Think Straight..., ca. 1960; 6477.PA0315; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Why You...America...And The Free World Need Nixon And Lodge, 1960; 6477.PA0316; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - America Needs Nixon Lodge, 1960; 6477.PA0317; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - 20 Questions About Jack Kennedy, ca. 1960; 6477.PA0318; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Record Of Senator John F. Kennedy On Civil Rights..., ca. 1960; 6477.PA0319; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The 1960 Democratic Fact Book, 1960; 6477.PA0320; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - A Pledge To The Working Man..., 1960; 6477.PA0321; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Here's What The Democrats Think About Kennedy!, 1960; 6477.PA0322; Items: 2 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Kennedy, John F. (Anti)
  - Facts For New York Voters: Kennedy For President..., 1960; 6477.PA0323; Items: 2 (Box 11)
    Party: Democtatic
  - A Look At The Record From Labor's Viewpoint, 1960; 6477.PA0324; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - I Need Women... (Sketch of Uncle Sam, pointing), ca. 1960; 6477.PA0325; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - I Need Men... (Sketch of Uncle Sam, pointing), ca. 1960; 6477.PA0326; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - The Big Difference...Vote Liberal For Kennedy & Johnson, 1960; 6477.PA0327; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Dear Fellow Historian (Fund-raising letter for Congressman George McGovern), ca. 1960; 6477.PA0328; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Leadership For The 60's Kennedy For President, 1960; 6477.PA0329; Items: 2 (Box 17)
  - Vote Intelligently Vote Conscientiously...(Christopher Notes, No. 107), 1960; 6477.PA0330; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Presidential 1960 Handbook, 1960; 6477.PA0331; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Our American Government What Is It? How Does It Function?, 1960; 6477.PA0332; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - State Of New York Department Of State...Text Of Proposition Number One..., 1960; 6477.PA0333; Items: 4 (Box 11)
  - John And Mary Blake And The Brannan Plan (Comic Paper format), ca. 1950; 6477.PA0334; Items: 2 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Brannan, Charles F.
  - Georgetown College Journal April 1912, 1912; 6477.PA0335; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Lehman A Governor Corageous..., ca. 1936; 6477.PA0336; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Lehman, Herbert H.
  - Official Program Inaugural Ceremonies of John F. Kennedy..., 1961; 6477.PA0337; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Friends Of The Rockefeller Team...Let Youth Help You Win Elections!, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0338; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller Roundup No. 2, 1970; 6477.PA0339; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Some reasons Why, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0340; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Re-Elect Rockefeller Experience Makes The Difference, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0341; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot. He'll do More! (Blue lettering), ca. 1970; 6477.PA0342; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot, He'll do More. (Green lettering), ca. 1970; 6477.PA0343; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For the Aging, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0344; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For The Arts, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0345; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For Businessmen, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0346; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For the Environment, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0347; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For Health, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0348; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For Higher Education, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0349; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For Labor, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0350; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Rockefeller He's Done A Lot...For Recreation, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0351; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Field Manual Independents For Rockefeller, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0352; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Field Canvasser's Guide Independents For Rockefeller, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0353; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Independents For Rockefeller Canvasser's Kit (Folders, bags, pamphlets), 1970; 6477.PA0354; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz, 1970; 6477.PA0355; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Consumer Protection A Statement From Louis J. Lefkowitz, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0356; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Your ABC's Of Careful Buying, ca. 1970; 6477.PA0357; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Civil Rights In New York State, 1968; 6477.PA0358; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - 20 Ways Not To Be Gypped, 1970; 6477.PA0359; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Mission 70's Handbook For Committeemen, 1970; 6477.PA0360; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Republican: 1970 Republican Party Reference Manual Tompkins County, 1970; 6477.PA0361; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - On Nov. 3 Vote James Buckley For U.S. Senator, 1970; 6477.PA0362; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - James L. Buckley for United States Senator, 1970; 6477.PA0363; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Guts, 1970; 6477.PA0364; Items: 2 (Box 11)
    Party: Liberal
  - Every Politician Faces The Difficult Choice...Senator Charles Goodell..., 1970; 6477.PA0365; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - He's Too Good To Lose, 1970; 6477.PA0366; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Senator Goodell...He's Your Man In Washington, 1970; 6477.PA0367; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Integrity, Experience, Concern Goldberg Paterson (Photo of Goldberg), 1970; 6477.PA0368; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Goldberg, Arthur J.
  - Integrity, Experience, Concern Goldberg/Paterson (Photo of both), 1970; 6477.PA0369; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Tompkins County Needs Arthur Goldberg Basil Paterson, 1970; 6477.PA0370; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Howard Samuels Speaks Out On The Issues, 1970; 6477.PA0371; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Samuels, Howard
  - Only Howard Samuels, 1970; 6477.PA0372; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Ottinger Delivers, 1970; 6477.PA0373; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Ottinger, Richard L.
  - Misgivings About Ottinger (The City Politic, By Gloria Steinem), 1970; 6477.PA0374; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Connie Cook's Legislative Report, 1970; 6477.PA0375; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Re-Elect Constance Cook Republican Candidate New York State Assembly, 1970; 6477.PA0376; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - The Liberal Party Story, 1970; 6477.PA0377; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - American Party Objectives And Principles, 1970; 6477.PA0378; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Ed Lawton and Ken MacPherson Vote American Independent Party, 1970; 6477.PA0379; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Lawton, Edwin G.
    Party: American Independent
  - Movement For A New Congress, 1970; 6477.PA0380; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Daniel Button District 29 Movement For A New Congress, 1970; 6477.PA0381; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Button, Daniel
  - Elect Bruce G. Dean Republican Candidate For Tompkins County Judge..., 1970; 6477.PA0382; Items: 2 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Dean, Bruce G.
  - The New Democrat (Vol. 1, No's 5 and 6), 1970; 6477.PA0383; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Keep The Trains Running (Newspaper cCipping), n/a; 6477.PA0384; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Candidates And Issues...League Of Women Voters Of Tompkins County, 1970; 6477.PA0385; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Facts For Voters...League Of Women Voters Of New York State, 1970; 6477.PA0386; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - A Liberal Legislative Action Program For 1970, 1970; 6477.PA0387; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - O'Dwyer '70 A Man Of Action A Man Of Peace A Man Of Honor, 1970; 6477.PA0388; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - N.Y. Swings To Buckley (Buckley News. Edition 2), 1970; 6477.PA0389; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Alliance Against Deprivation (Excerpts From A Speech...), 1967; 6477.PA0390; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Better Idea (Excerpts From A Speech...), 1968; 6477.PA0391; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Civil Order, Social Justice (Excerpts From A Speech...), 1968; 6477.PA0392; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Humanity's Rights (Excerpts From A Speech...), 1968; 6477.PA0393; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Marshall Plan For Our Cities (Excerpts From A Speech...), 1968; 6477.PA0394; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Humphrey Muskie Two You Can Trust, 1968; 6477.PA0395; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Why Labor Supports U.S. Senator Jacob K. Javits..., 1968; 6477.PA0396; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Vote For Javits, 1968; 6477.PA0397; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Christianity And Crisis...Hubert Humphrey For President, 1968; 6477.PA0398; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Calling All Delegates (Reprinted from The New Republic, July 27, 1968), 1968; 6477.PA0399; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - McCarthy For President (Information Packet), 1968; 6477.PA0400; Items: 8 (Box 9)
  - Courage Is Contagious, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0401; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Eugene McCarthy On the Record, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0402; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - In three Months Eugene McCarthy Has Set America Free, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0403; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The McCarthy Advance (Vol. 1, no's 4 and 5, July 4 and 18 1968), 1968; 6477.PA0404; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - McCarthy Now! The New York Weekly Newsletter (Vol 1, no's 1, 2 and 4), 1968; 6477.PA0405; Items: 3 (Box 9)
  - Statement By Senator Eugene McCarthy (On the Grape Strike, 8/1/68), 1968; 6477.PA0406; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Eugene J. Mccarthy On Hunger In America, 1968; 6477.PA0407; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Eugene J. Mccarthy On Poverty Welfare Housing Education, 1968; 6477.PA0408; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Eugene J. McCarthy "Toward An Open America", 1968; 6477.PA0409; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - McCarthy On The Democratic Party, 1968; 6477.PA0410; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Eugene McCarthy Democratizing the Democratic Party, 1968; 6477.PA0411; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Campaign for A Democratic Alternative ...McCarthy For President (Letter), 1968; 6477.PA0412; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - July 20th Rally Committee Inter-Block Council for Peace (Letter), 1968; 6477.PA0413; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - McCarthy For President Coalition For A Democratic Alternative (Press Release), 1968; 6477.PA0414; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Coalition For A Democratic Alternative (Press Release June 10, 1968), 1968; 6477.PA0415; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Missouri Democrats Endorse McCarthy, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0416; Items: 1 (Box 10)
  - McCarthy Campaign Analysis Staff Memorandum, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0417; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - People for McCarthy Letter Writing Campaign (List of County Chairmen), ca. 1968; 6477.PA0418; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - New York Local Headquarters And Coordinators, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0419; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - New York McCarthy Delegate Slates May 24, 1968, 1968; 6477.PA0420; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - McCarthy For President List Of District Delegates Elected...New York State..., 1968; 6477.PA0421; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - McCarthy For President Delegates-At-Large Chosen...By The New York State..., 1968; 6477.PA0422; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Letter Canvassers Materials in Blue Folder, 1968; 6477.PA0423; Items: 12 (Box 11)
  - Contact List (McCarthy Campaign), ca. 1968; 6477.PA0424; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Democrat May 1967 (Democratic National Committee Magazine), 1967; 6477.PA0425; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Victory '68 News From United Democrats For Humphrey August 5, 1968, 1968; 6477.PA0426; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Humphrey VS. Nixon 1948-1968 Twenty Years Of Contrast, 1968; 6477.PA0427; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Humphrey And Nixon Speak On Labor, 1968; 6477.PA0428; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Women Know...The Best Possible Education, ca. 1968; 6477.PA0429; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Republican Platform Adopted At Chicago June 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0430; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Election: 1888
  - To the Wage-Earners Of The United States..., 1888; 6477.PA0431; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Cleveland, Grover (Anti)
  - Protection to the Farmer, 1888; 6477.PA0432; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Farmers! Read This!! Why You Should Vote the Democratic Ticket..., 1888; 6477.PA0433; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Cleveland, Grover
  - A Fable, 1888; 6477.PA0434; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Samuel J. Randall
    Party: Protection Democrat
  - What Tariff Reform Means!!, 1888; 6477.PA0435; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Voice. Extra...May 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0436; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Fisk, Clinton B.
  - Protection For Farmers (New York Tribune Extra no. 98, April, 1888), 1888; 6477.PA0437; Items: 1 (Box 18)